Enter the library window and double-click on the end-of-day file named Elton and enter femalev2.
Double-click on the file fv2vv.mvt and drag it into the 3D window.
Open the Proteus Files folder in the library window and find bimbasic.jacket and double-click on the file jacket-femur.dxf or drag it into the 2D or 3D window.
In the 2D window, select all the files.
On the file, there is a button.
In the menu, select the column-linked files, match the files, and deny the line.
Copy the other half of the match.
Press Shift to move the file to the other side.
In the 2D window, select the back and collar that are copied.
Move the file to near the back of the original back.
In the 3D tool bar, select all 2D arrangement positions.
Align the 2D window to the 3D window.
Align the mouse to the fourth in the 3D vertical tool bar.
Click on the display arrangement point.
The blue arrangement point will be displayed around the 3D window virtual model.
In the 2D window, select all the files.
Press Ctrl and A to select all the files.
Move the file to the arrangement point that is blocked.
There is a layer relationship between the front and the back.
Use the position tool to put the back of the back of the front.
You can rotate the view to see the distance between the files.
You can also rotate the view to the left and right.
Now you can see between the front and the back.
There is also a layer relationship between the front and left.
Press Shift in the 2D window.
At the same time, select the left and right front of the back to make a 3D panel.
In the 3D window, use the position tool to move the front right to the front left.
Put the right front piece to the top of the left front piece
You can rotate the view to see the distance between the panels
There is also a layer relationship between the difference between the back pieces
In the 3D window, click on the right back piece
Use the positioning tool
Put the right back panel to the top of the left back piece
You can rotate the view to see the gap between the panels
In the 2D window, hold down the Shift key
Select the front panel and the hanging panel
Move the mouse to the 3D window
Press the left button on the pre-arrangement point
Arrange the panels around the model
Select the front panel
Click on the Arrangement point in the 3D window
Adjust the position of the external axis in the mouse pointer
Place the panel in the right position
Rotate the view to the back view or press the shortcut key
Rotate the view to the back view
Press the Shift key in the 2D window
Select the back panel at the same time
In the 3D window, press the Arrangement point in the back
Arrange the panels around the model
In the 2D window, select the panel on the back side
In the 3D window, press the Arrangement point and place the panel
By editing the data arranged by the model, adjust the position of the panel
Rotate the view to the left view
Arrange the sleeves to the arm arrangement point
Arrange the collar to the neck point
Arrange the mouse to the fourth of the vertical tool bar
Click on the Arrangement point to hide the arrangement point
In the 3D window, press the Shift key in the 3D window
Rotate the view to the right view
Use the Seam Seaming tool to sew the front and back
Make sure the seam direction is consistent
In the 3D window, press the Seam Seaming tool to hide the arrangement point
Sew the sleeves and the sleeves
Pay attention to the seam direction when sewing
Thread the fabric in the same way
Sew the collar to the collar
Pay attention to the seam direction
Change the face to the front piece.
Change the function type to Turn in the sound editor.
After activating the simulation, the face will be more flat.
In the 3D tool bar, select the button button.
Click on the base line of the button button in the front piece.
The button button line will appear on the 2D version.
At the same time, the button button line will appear on the 2D version.
The image of the button button will appear in 3D.
In the 3D tool bar, use the Move Button Tool to select the button button in the 2D window.
Click on the button button in the 2D window.
Select the button button in the menu and copy the button to the symmetrical version.
The line of the button button will appear on the symmetrical version.
At the same time, the button button image will appear in 3D.
In the 2D window, select Button and Button Button.
Click on the button on the right of the button and select the parameter to be set in the menu.
In the dialogue box, enter the value 2.
A symbol that indicates the button and the buttonhole will appear on the screen.
Use the move button tool to adjust the position of the button and buttonhole on the screen.
In the 3D tool bar, select the new button tool.
In the 2D window, select the button and move the mouse to the button.
The button pessure will stop.
Ezra shows the model face.
The model is naturally circled on the virtual model.
Turn off the modeling.
Use the move button key toemorize the start and end of the model.
In the level menu in the window bar,
Select OK by Employee Wonky.
Click on the box and enter the button vault.
Select the
In the preview, you can choose the type of
The setting of the fire simulation is used on the 3D clothing
In the 2D tool bar, select the tool
Press the Shift key in the window
Select the front and the side of the front panel
Press the
Put the base line as the internal line
Select the
Press the
Set the base line to the inner line.
In the 3D tool bar, select the folding arrangement tool.
On the 3D clothing, click on the newly created folding line on the 0 version.
It will display the folding arrangement positioning ball.
Drag the arrow to fold the collar, and repeat the operation on the other side.
In the 2D tool bar, select the editor version tool.
Select the folding line on the 0 version.
In the audio editor, adjust the folding angle to 360 degrees.
In the 3D window, use the folding arrangement tool.
Select the newly created folding line on the front outer layer.
It will display the folding arrangement positioning ball.
Drag the arrow to fold the collar, and repeat the operation on the other side.
When folding, pay attention to avoid overlapping with the outer layer.
In the audio editor, adjust the folding angle of the front and the outer layer to 360 degrees.
In the audio editor, adjust the folding angle to 360 degrees.
In the 3D window, select the folding arrangement tool.
Press the share button.
At the same time, select the 0 version, the front, and the cover.
On the version, right-click on the menu.
Click on the menu to select hardening.
You can make the version temporary edit and fold more easily.
Activate the simulation to make the collar folded.
The evaluation of clothes for cover is better.
Press the W button on the keyboard to produce a set-point.
Pull the set-point to make the collar more even.
Press the W button to create a set-point.
Turn off the simulation.
In the 3D window,
Press the shift key to close it.
Select the front panel panel at the same time.
Click on the panel.
Select the hardening in the menu.
Open the simulation.
Make the panel simulation natural.
After the simulation is complete, close the simulation.
Select the view to the rear view.
In the 2D tool bar, select the frame tool.
Select the base line that needs folding.
Press the reverse key to fold it into the internal line.
In the 3D tool bar, select the folding arrangement tool.
In the 3D window, select the newly created folding line.
Use the folding arrangement tool to fold the back.
Just fold the back of the right back.
To make the folding more accurate, set the folding angle to 0 in the attribute editor.
Activate the simulation.
Make the settings apply to 3D clothing.
After the simulation is complete, close the simulation.
The left back and the right back have a link,
but the left back is not used.
It needs to be folded.
Press the control Z key on the keyboard to withdraw.
In the 2D window, click on the right button on the back panel.
Select the remove link in the pop-up menu.
Remove the link between the panels.
Select the folding line on the left back panel.
Press the delete key to delete the folding line.
Activate the simulation.
In the 2D window, use the folding arrangement tool to fold the back.
Use the folding arrangement tool to fold the right back.
Do the same on the 2D window.
The folding line will be realized.
In the motif editor, change the folding line type to Turn.
After activating the simulation, the effect number will be more flat.
Enter the library window.
In the Elta document, double-click.
Enter FemaleV2.
Open the Post.
Double-click on the FV203 document
or drag it to the 3D window.
Change the model's posture to a vertical one.
Go to the window of the canvas and double-click on the file named Fabric.
Select Cotton Garbage.
Drag it into the object window on Fabric.
Activate the simulation and apply the settings to 3D clothing.
In the 2D window, use the editor tool.
In the middle of the collar, right-click and select Comparison in the menu.
Comparison the collar.
In the edge of the model, select the double-click on Fabric.
Activate the simulation and apply the settings to 3D clothing.
In the middle of the model, select the double-click on Fabric.
Activate the simulation.
Turn off the simulation when the simulation is complete.
The collar needs two layers.
The collar needs to be thicker.
Click on the object window and drag the material down in the material editor.
You can see the thickness of this fabric.
In the 2D and 3D windows, select the plate.
In the option of adding the thickness of the wool material in the material editor,
enter the thickness value of the fabric.
In the upper part of the material editor,
Select the double-layer window next to the double-layer display on the selected line on the top of the screen.
In the 3D window, you can see the double-layer effect of the collar.
In the 3D tool bar, select the tool to improve the quality of the clothing.
Click OK when the contrast light is turned on.
Open the simulation and apply the settings to the 3D clothing.
Close the simulation after the simulation is completed.